Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Episode 17= (I am fond of you too)
=الحلقة 17= (أنا معجب بك أيضاً)
Yan.
نعم.
Young Madam,
سيدتي الشابة،
what is wrong?
ما المشكلة؟
How long has it been since Yan last wrote home?
كم مضى من الوقت منذ أن كتب يان آخر مرة إلى أهله؟
It has been almost half a month, has it not?
لقد مرّ ما يقارب نصف شهر، أليس كذلك؟
I heard that the Young Master is succeeding in the bandit suppression
سمعت أن السيد الشاب ينجح في قمع قطاع الطرق.
and should be returning soon.
ومن المتوقع عودته قريباً.
Master,
يتقن،
Xie Yunyan is missing,
شيه يونيان مفقود.
and there is no news of him.
ولا توجد أي أخبار عنه.
I suspects
أظن
he feigned death to escape
تظاهر بالموت للهروب
and is after the ledger.
ويأتي بعد دفتر الأستاذ.
Then tell Wen Zhihu
ثم أخبر Wen Zhihu
to set a trap
نصب فخ
and wait for him to fall into it.
وانتظر حتى يقع في الفخ.
Yes.
نعم.
Wait.
انتظر.
As for the Xiao Manor,
أما بالنسبة لقصر شياو،
when can I get the item I requested?
متى يمكنني الحصول على المنتج الذي طلبته؟
I will go and handle it immediately.
سأذهب وأتعامل مع الأمر فوراً.
Young Lady Su,
الشابة سو،
Yan has met with trouble.
واجه يان مشكلة.
Yan was suppressing bandits
كان يان يقمع قطاع الطرق
and entered the bandits' stronghold alone.
ودخل معقل قطاع الطرق بمفرده.
He is missing.
إنه مفقود.
No body has been found
لم يتم العثور على أي جثة
alive or dead.
حياً أو ميتاً.
Disaster relief can win over the people's hearts.
يمكن للإغاثة في حالات الكوارث أن تكسب قلوب الناس.
Suppressing the rebellion can consolidate military power.
إن قمع التمرد من شأنه أن يعزز القوة العسكرية.
This is the Xiao family's best opportunity.
هذه هي أفضل فرصة لعائلة شياو.
(I might return a bit later,)
(قد أعود بعد قليل،)
(do not worry about me.)
(لا تقلق عليّ.)
Yan will be fine. I will also send people privately to look for him.
سيكون يان بخير. سأرسل أيضاً أشخاصاً بشكل خاص للبحث عنه.
Young Lady Su, you do not need to worry too much.
يا آنسة سو، لا داعي للقلق كثيراً.
The Xiao family is already like this.
عائلة شياو هكذا بالفعل.
Why are you still coming to find me?
لماذا ما زلت تأتي للبحث عني؟
Huo Rou,
هوو رو,
do you truly believe Master sent you into the Xiao Manor
هل تعتقد حقاً أن السيد أرسلك إلى قصر شياو؟
to bear children for the Xiao family?
لإنجاب الأطفال لعائلة شياو؟
Do not forget,
لا تنسَ،
you entered the Xiao Manor
لقد دخلت قصر شياو
to retrieve the Xiao family's private seal.
لاستعادة الختم الخاص بعائلة شياو.
If the Xiao family's private seal were so easy to find,
لو كان من السهل العثور على الختم الخاص بعائلة شياو ،
Master would not have gone to such lengths to send me in.
لم يكن السيد ليذهب إلى هذا الحد لإرسالي إلى الداخل.
Now, the Xiao family
الآن، عائلة شياو
is managed by Su Jinyuan.
يديرها سو جينيوان.
That woman is very cunning.
تلك المرأة ماكرة جداً.
If I act rashly and she discovers me,
إذا تصرفت بتهور واكتشفتني،
ruining Master's great plan,
إفساد خطة السيد العظيمة،
can you bear the responsibility?
هل يمكنك تحمل المسؤولية؟
Is it that you had no opportunity,
هل لم تتح لك الفرصة؟
or that you simply do not want to do it?
أم أنك ببساطة لا تريد القيام بذلك؟
Xie Yunyan is not at home now.
شي يون يان ليست في المنزل الآن.
This is your best chance.
هذه هي فرصتك الأفضل.
If that Su Jinyuan gets in the way,
إذا وقفت سو جينيوان في طريقنا،
then eliminate her.
ثم تخلص منها.
If she dies,
إذا ماتت،
Xie Yunyan will not let it go when he returns.
لن يتخلى شي يون يان عن الأمر عندما يعود.
Do not worry.
لا تقلق.
Xie Yunyan is already beyond returning.
لقد أصبح من المستحيل عودة شي يون يان.
That little brat, thinking he is so smart and talking nonsense,
ذلك الطفل الصغير المزعج، يظن نفسه ذكياً جداً ويتحدث بكلام فارغ،
even attempting to feign death to escape and find the ledger.
حتى أنهم حاولوا التظاهر بالموت للهروب والعثور على دفتر الحسابات.
Our men have been waiting for him in Xianyang for a long time.
رجالنا ينتظرونه في شيانيانغ منذ فترة طويلة.
(Memorial Tablet of Xiao Yue and Zhang Fen)
(لوحة تذكارية لـ شياو يو وتشانغ فين)
Jinyuan, you have been kneeling for a whole day.
جينيوان، لقد كنت راكعاً طوال اليوم.
Have some ginseng soup.
تناول بعض حساء الجينسنغ.
Rou,
رو،
is there anything else
هل هناك أي شيء آخر؟
added to your soup?
هل أضفتها إلى حسائك؟
When Yan left,
عندما غادر يان،
he told me everything.
أخبرني بكل شيء.
Your Third Sister-in-Law
أخت زوجك الثالثة
almost lost the child in her belly
كادت أن تفقد الطفل الذي في رحمها
because of poison.
بسبب السم.
Poison?
سم؟
And it is not a common poison.
وهو ليس سماً شائعاً.
It is specifically used to control spies.
يُستخدم تحديداً للسيطرة على الجواسيس.
Sixth Young Master Xie,
السيد الشاب السادس شيه،
your Third Sister-in-Law is not simple.
إنّ التعامل مع أخت زوجك الثالثة ليس بالأمر السهل.
She is a member of your Xiao family.
إنها فرد من عائلة شياو الخاصة بك.
To save her or not,
إنقاذها أم لا،
give me an answer.
أعطني إجابة.
Are you suspecting
هل تشك في ذلك؟
that I poisoned you?
هل تقصد أنني سممتك؟
The Xiao Manor is being watched.
قصر شياو يخضع للمراقبة.
I had to put on a show
كان عليّ أن أقدم عرضاً
so they would not be suspicious.
حتى لا يثيروا الشكوك.
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
I am a spy who was sent into the Xiao Manor.
أنا جاسوس أُرسلت إلى قصر شياو.
Rou,
رو،
can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
why you have the spy's poison in your system?
لماذا يوجد سم الجاسوس في جسمك؟
I do not know what you are talking about.
لا أعرف عما تتحدث.
No wonder Third Brother specifically instructed me
لا عجب أن الأخ الثالث أعطاني تعليمات محددة
before he set off on the campaign,
قبل أن ينطلق في حملته الانتخابية،
that no matter what happened later,
بغض النظر عما سيحدث لاحقاً،
I had to protect you.
كان عليّ حمايتك.
Are you saying
هل تقول
Third Brother already knew I was...
كان أخي الثالث يعلم بالفعل أنني...
Yes.
نعم.
Third Brother knew you were a spy all along.
كان الأخ الثالث يعلم أنك جاسوس طوال الوقت.
He wholeheartedly protected you,
لقد حماك بكل إخلاص،
but what about you?
لكن ماذا عنك؟
You were focused on scheming against the Xiao family.
كنتَ تركز على التآمر ضد عائلة شياو.
The Xiao family towards you,
عائلة شياو تتقدم إليكم،
and Third Brother toward you, were they not good enough?
والأخ الثالث تجاهك، ألم يكونوا كافيين؟
Who exactly
من هو بالضبط
is trying to target the Xiao family?
هل يحاول استهداف عائلة شياو؟
I cannot say.
لا أستطيع أن أقول.
The Xiao family was truly good to me.
لقد كانت عائلة شياو لطيفة معي حقاً.
Third Brother was also good.
كان فيلم "الأخ الثالث" جيداً أيضاً.
You all gave me a home.
لقد منحتموني جميعاً بيتاً.
I even have a child now.
بل إن لدي طفلاً الآن.
But my life
لكن حياتي
was given by my Master.
أعطاني إياها سيدي.
He picked me up from a pile of dead bodies,
انتشلني من بين كومة من الجثث،
gave me food,
أعطاني طعاماً،
and gave me clothes.
وأعطاني ملابس.
The moment I took the poison,
في اللحظة التي تناولت فيها السم،
I already had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار آخر.
You do have a choice.
لديك خيار.
I promised Third Brother
لقد وعدت الأخ الثالث
that I would protect you.
أنني سأحميك.
The prerequisite is
الشرط الأساسي هو
that I only protect the Xiao family members.
أنني لا أحمي سوى أفراد عائلة شياو.
When you and Yan
عندما كنت أنت ويان
saved my life
أنقذ حياتي
and saved my child,
وأنقذت طفلي،
I never thought about betraying the Xiao family again.
لم أفكر أبداً في خيانة عائلة شياو مرة أخرى.
Yan
يان
must have gone to Xianyang to look for evidence against them.
لا بد أنهم ذهبوا إلى شيانيانغ للبحث عن أدلة ضدهم.
He might fall into their trap.
قد يقع في فخهم.
Jinyuan,
جينيوان،
I have prepared the carriage.
لقد جهزت العربة.
While it is still dark,
بينما لا يزال الظلام حالكاً،
you must quickly go find Yan.
يجب عليك أن تذهب بسرعة للعثور على يان.
I will stop by Xinglin Hall for some medicine,
سأتوقف عند قاعة شينغلين لأخذ بعض الأدوية.
just to be safe.
من باب الاحتياط فقط.
Go quickly.
انطلق بسرعة.
I will wait for you here.
سأنتظرك هنا.
Huo Rou.
هوو رو.
Serve the dishes.
قدّم الأطباق.
One moment, please.
لحظة من فضلك.
Yan.
نعم.
Yuan.
يوان.
♪Lost in the maze, waves rising♪
♪ضائع في المتاهة، والأمواج ترتفع♪
♪A whirlpool layer by layer♪
♪ دوامة طبقة تلو الأخرى ♪
♪Stumbling through the story♪
♪أتعثر في سرد ​​القصة♪
♪Threads tangled and knotted♪
♪خيوط متشابكة ومعقدة♪
♪Beneath the face I wear♪
♪خلف القناع الذي أرتديه♪
♪Lies a form I know so well♪
♪يوجد شكل أعرفه جيداً♪
♪Still struggling and wandering♪
♪ما زلتُ أكافح وأتجول♪
♪Time refuses to unlock♪
♪الوقت يرفض أن يفتح ♪
♪Half a lifetime shared with you♪
نصف عمرٍ قضيته معك
♪Thoughts rise then fall♪
♪ترتفع الأفكار ثم تهبط♪
♪In the dark we wrote one small flame of hope♪
♪في الظلام كتبنا شعلة أمل صغيرة♪
If you are worried,
إذا كنت قلقاً،
why not openly go with her?
لماذا لا تذهب معها علنًا؟
Is First Young Master Xiao really planning
هل يخطط السيد الشاب الأول شياو حقاً؟
to keep watching her from the shadows?
أن نستمر في مراقبتها من الظلال؟
Even if your affection is as deep as the sea,
حتى لو كان حبك عميقاً كالبحر،
it is like a mute performing for a blind person.
يشبه الأمر أداء شخص أبكم لشخص أعمى.
She will never know.
لن تعرف أبداً.
This is actually fine.
هذا جيد في الواقع.
I do not want...
لا أريد...
You do not want what?
ماذا لا تريد؟
You are such a good person,
أنت شخص طيب للغاية،
and you already had a marriage agreement with her.
وكان لديك بالفعل اتفاقية زواج معها.
After spending a long time together, she will definitely come to like you.
بعد قضاء وقت طويل معاً، ستحبك بالتأكيد.
Why do you torture yourself?
لماذا تعذب نفسك؟
If you truly like her,
إذا كنت معجباً بها حقاً،
you should let her know of your presence,
ينبغي عليك إخبارها بوجودك.
know your feelings,
اعرف مشاعرك،
know that you are fond of her,
أعلم أنك معجب بها،
and that you care for her.
وأنك تهتم لأمرها.
Young Lady Xi,
الشابة شي،
if there were any possibility,
لو كان هناك أي احتمال،
I would tell her every single word without fail.
كنت سأخبرها بكل كلمة دون استثناء.
But now I am a dying man.
لكنني الآن رجل يحتضر.
She and Yan are also deeply in love.
هي ويان أيضاً مغرمان ببعضهما بشدة.
Towards her,
تجاهها،
I can feel respect,
أشعر بالاحترام،
and gratitude,
مع خالص الشكر والامتنان،
but absolutely
لكن بالتأكيد
no romantic feelings.
لا توجد مشاعر رومانسية.
She and I are ultimately not meant to be.
في نهاية المطاف، لم يكن مقدراً لنا أن نكون معاً.
The only thing I can do now is help them achieve their happiness.
الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكنني فعله الآن هو مساعدتهم على تحقيق سعادتهم.
Do not worry, Yunxi.
لا تقلق، يونشي.
I will certainly cure you.
سأشفيك بالتأكيد.
I know what you want to ask.
أعرف ما تريد أن تسأل عنه.
But you cannot defeat him.
لكن لا يمكنك هزيمته.
Tell Yan,
أخبر يان،
the matter of the Xiao family
مسألة عائلة شياو
is already set in stone.
أمرٌ محسومٌ بالفعل.
But Yan and I
لكن يان وأنا
do not want to accept our fate.
لا نريد أن نقبل مصيرنا.
When Third Brother set off on the campaign,
عندما انطلق الأخ الثالث في الحملة،
why did I not tell him
لماذا لم أخبره؟
that I was truly fond of him?
هل كنتُ معجبة به حقاً؟
Until he died,
حتى وفاته،
I never had another chance to tell him.
لم تتح لي فرصة أخرى لإخباره.
Yuan.
يوان.
I am finally free.
أنا حر أخيراً.
Just let my ashes turn to dust
دع رمادي يتحول إلى غبار
and drift away with the water,
وتنجرف مع الماء،
to never
أن لا
meet again.
نلتقي مجدداً.
Yan,
نعم،
actually, the assassin was there to kill me.
في الحقيقة، كان القاتل موجوداً ليقتلني.
Rou saved me
رو أنقذني
and that is why she...
ولهذا السبب هي...
Do not worry.
لا تقلق.
I will certainly avenge Rou
سأنتقم بالتأكيد لرو
and the Xiao family.
وعائلة شياو.
Even if it means
حتى لو كان ذلك يعني
sacrificing my life.
التضحية بحياتي.
Yan,
نعم،
I do not want you to sacrifice yourself.
لا أريدك أن تضحي بنفسك.
I want you to live well.
أتمنى لك حياة طيبة.
Xie Yunyan,
شيه يونيان,
I do not want to die with hatred,
لا أريد أن أموت وأنا أحمل الكراهية،
like Huo Rou did,
كما فعل هيو رو،
and end up with regrets.
وينتهي الأمر بالندم.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
It was me who was trapped by identity,
كنت أنا من وقع في فخ الهوية،
making things difficult for you,
مما يجعل الأمور صعبة عليك،
and for myself.
ولنفسي أيضاً.
Actually, that day
في الواقع، في ذلك اليوم
when you said you were fond of me,
عندما قلت إنك معجب بي،
I was happy too.
كنت سعيداً أيضاً.
I am also fond of you.
أنا أيضاً معجب بك.
Actually, there is something
في الحقيقة، هناك شيء ما
I have been keeping from you for a long time.
لقد أخفيت عنك هذا الأمر لفترة طويلة.
Yunxi...
يونكسي...
He did not die.
لم يمت.
He came back a long time ago.
لقد عاد منذ زمن طويل.